opptrends.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy Policy | Opptrends

At opportunity trends this site opptrends.com, we respect your privacy and we will never sell, rent, or otherwise share your email address or any personal information to any third party. Disclosure of personal information from this site can only occur under one condition, and that is when required by law.

This privacy policy is made to give you comfort knowing your information is safe with us, but please note that this privacy policy is only applicable to this site, and not to any other website that you may visit from opptrends.com this site, other websites that may have different information collection, policies and terms.

The basic information we collect while operating this site may include visitors’ comments, newsletters, and other forms that may ask users for their emails, names, and any other contact information.

This basic information maybe used solely to contact you if and when needed and we may use your comments “anonymously” to provide meaningful content to others or to share ideas that we may deem beneficial to other users of this site.

We may use cookies in order to deliver content of specific interest to you or for other purposes and promoters and advertisers on this site may use cookies however, we have no control or access to the information collected by third party advertisers.

Other data is collected in aggregate by third party statistics providers in order to track site usage and traffic analysis.

 **We may share data with third parties for marketing and/or promotional purposes, as such:**

  * This site uses the Google Analytics features implemented based on Display Advertising (e.g., Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting).
  * You can use Google’s [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads), to opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads.
  * You can also use Google’s currently [available Opt-outs](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) for Browser Add-on.

This site has links to other websites, if you choose to visit other websites, we have no access to or control over their privacy policies and content. Please note that it is your choice and responsibility to review their policies and understand and agree with them.

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy, or this site in general, or to have your information removed from our database, please feel free to contact us by clicking the contact link on the above menu in this page or send us email:

opptrends”at”gmail.com

We reserve the right to add to, change, update or modify this policy at any time and without notice and any changes, modification, updates or additions will be effective immediately upon publishing on this site.
